Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series XIII. Vassar Paintings and Historical Images, 1900-1940
  - Ann (Bennett) Vassar — Image of a painting of Ann (Bennett) Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_09])
  - Catherine (Valentine) Vassar — Image of a painting of Catherine (Valentine) Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_10])
  - Catherine (Valentine) Vassar — Image of a painting of Catherine (Valentine) Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_11])
  - James Monroe Taylor — Image of a photograph of James Monroe Taylor, 1909-1940 (Box 99 [Box260_007])
  - James Monroe Taylor — Image of a photograph of James Monroe Taylor, 1909-1940 (Box 43/44 [Box279_016])
  - James Vassar — Image of a painting of James Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_06])
  - John Howard Raymond — Image of a photograph of John Howard Raymond, 1900-1940 (Box 8 [Package034_003])
  - Lodge — Copy photograph of the Lodge, 1900-1940 (Box 35/36 [Box268_017])
  - Main Building — Copy photograph of a photograph of Main Building, 1900-1940 (Box 35/36 [Box268_004])
  - Main Building — Copy photograph of a photograph of Main Building, 1900-1940 (Box 35/36 [Box268_005])
  - Main Building — Copy photograph of Main Building, 1900-1940 (Box 35/36 [Box268_018])
  - Maria Mitchell — Copy photograph of a photograph of Maria Mitchell, 1900-1940 (Box 31 [Box261_007])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a miniature portrait of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_03])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a painting of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_04])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a painting of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_07])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a painting of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_08])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a photograph of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 99 [Box260_002])
  - Matthew Vassar — Copy photograph of a photograph of Matthew Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 99 [Box260_009])
  - Thomas Vassar — Copy photograph of a painting of Thomas Vassar, 1900-1940 (Box 74 [223_16])